Xiaoning.
You scared me.
Why are you here?
Where is Shiya?
Shiya is a bit cold.
She asked me to chop some firewood
to warm up.
Let me do it.
No thanks.
I got this.
Xiaoning,
I happen to have a question for you too.
When did you...
When did you meet Shiya?
At our wedding?
Earlier.
Earlier?
In college.
College?
We were in the same grade.
Why don't I remember that?
Not long after school started,
I heard
she dropped out
because her family was in debt.
The next time we met
was at your wedding.
Then,
does Shiya know you like her?
Bro.
Don't misunderstand.
For the three years you were with her,
Shiya and I
did nothing to betray you.
Xiaoning,
what I'm about to say,
you might not believe.
But if you marry Shiya,
she will die.
She will die at your wedding.
This joke
is going a bit too far.
Xiaoning.
I am not lying to you.
I really witnessed
Shiya die at your wedding.
Don't you believe me?
Do you think I would lie to you?
Brother,
of course I want to believe you.
Then,
but brother,
you should also believe me.
I will protect Shiya well.
Xiaoning.
Brother, you're awake.
You're going rock climbing?
Yeah.
Doesn't Shiya like it?
By the way, brother.
I remember you used to climb when you were free.
Why don't you teach me?
That way,
I can go with Shiya.
Okay.
I'll go get my gear from the car.
No need.
Look.
I have everything here.
You're still missing a chalk bag.
Xiaoning.
Come with me to the car to get a case of water.
Okay.
Safety first in rock climbing.
I'll go first.
Watch my route.
Okay.
Where did you go this time?
Just went to grab something.
Where's the rope here?
Shiya took it.
She said she went rock climbing.
Rock climbing?
Where did she go rock climbing?
I think it's the mountain to the east.
Shiya.
Could something have happened to Shiya?
Look there.
Shiya.
Call the police.
Call for help.
Shiya.
Calm down first.
Don't panic.
I'm here.
Here.
Grab it.
There's a handhold on your upper left.
And a foothold on your lower right.
Step firmly.
Stay close to the wall.
There.
There's another foothold.
Step firmly.
Hold on tight.
Come up a bit more.
I'll catch you.
Move forward.
Come on.
Three.
Shiya.
Come on, get up.
You scared me to death.
How are you?
Are you hurt anywhere?
No.
I'm fine.
What happened?
How could you be so careless?
I...
I didn't check the equipment well.
Sorry to make everyone worry.
Shiya is an experienced climber.
She shouldn't have made such a rookie mistake.
This rope...
Those who survive a disaster are destined for good fortune.
Should we
go to that bar from last time
to relax?
You are really carefree.
It's fine.
I was scared to death.
Let's go.
Brother, I'll help you pack.